

Jovita Morkūnė Quality Assurance Specialist

- +370 636 58227
- jovita.morkune@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/jovita-morkune/
- Kaunas, Lithuania

SUMMARY

I am responsible, diligent, attentive and have good interpersonal skills. I am used to an agile work environment and can quickly adapt to changing business requirements.

Over the past 5 years, I had an opportunity to work with culturally diverse teams, where I was focusing on ensuring a high level of quality in the work my team was doing.

Currently, I'm studying a lot to become a software QA engineer. I would love to join a software company where I could create value by contributing to the quality assurance of interesting software products while also gaining more practical experience.

EXPERIENCE

Quality Improvement Specialist

03/2016 - 02/2020

R1 RCM

- Ensured the high-quality work of my team specialists.
- Improved several processes with macro commands to work processes in a more effective way and to avoid repetitive
 errors.
- Initiated additional projects with other teams, which helped to generate more income for the company.
- Investigated many trends and issues related to rejected claims, in order to resolve it faster and prevent more rejections.

Account Resolution Specialist

05/2015 - 03/2016

Intermedix

- Identified reasons for denied insurance claims and effectively resolved them by determining a course of action in the revenue cycle management system.
- Maintained high productivity and work quality results.
- Worked on various projects, collaborated with team members to reach the team goals.

EDUCATION

International Business 2018

Kaunas University of Technology - Master's degree

Finance 2015

Kaunas University of Technology - Bachelor's degree

CERTIFICATES

End to End Testing with Cypress: CodeMash (Pluralsight) 04/2020 - Present

JavaScript Essential Training (LinkedIn) 04/2020 - Present

Learning SQL Programming (LinkedIn) 03/2020 - Present

End-to-End JavaScript Testing with Cypress.io (LinkedIn) 03/2020 - Present

Programming Foundations: Software Testing/QA (LinkedIn) 03/2020 - Present

Global Collaboration Certificate (X-Culture)

12/2017 - Present

SKILLS

TeamworkExpertJavaScriptBeginnerQuality AssuranceAdvancedHTML/CSSBeginnerAnalytical SkillsAdvancedMongoDBBeginner

JIRA Intermediate

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate Lithuanian Native

Russian Basic